<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>
<release xmlns:xsi="http://www.w3.org/2001/XMLSchema-instance" xsi:noNamespaceSchemaLocation="../schema.xsd" version="14.0.1">
  <changelog href="https://nextcloud.com/changelog/#14-0-1"/>
  <whatsNew lang="en">
    <regular>
      <item>Several detail improvements in the user interface</item>
      <item>e.g. light icons with the dark theme</item>
      <item>or avoid overlapping the submit button in comments</item>
    </regular>
    <admin>
      <item>Treated issues with uncommon user IDs</item>
      <item>Fixed web logout on OAuth use</item>
      <item>Resolved false positive in server setup check</item>
    </admin>
  </whatsNew>
  <whatsNew lang="cs">
    <regular>
      <item>Několik drobných vylepšení v uživatelském rozhraní</item>
      <item>např. světlé ikony v tmavém motivu vzhledu</item>
      <item>nebo vyhnout se překrývání tlačítka odeslat v komentářích</item>
    </regular>
    <admin>
      <item>Ošetřeny problémy s neobvyklými identifikátory uživatelů</item>
      <item>Opraveno odhlašování z webu při použití OAuth</item>
      <item>Vyřešen falešný poplach při kontrole nastavení serveru</item>
    </admin>
  </whatsNew>
  <whatsNew lang="de">
    <regular>
      <item>Diverse Detailverbesserungen in der Benutzeroberfläche</item>
      <item>Z.B. helle Symbole mit dem dunklen Thema</item>
      <item>oder die Überlappung des Bestätigungs-Button in Kommentaren behoben</item>
    </regular>
    <admin>
      <item>Behandelte Probleme mit ungewöhnlichen Benutzer-IDs</item>
      <item>Fehler beim Web-Logout bei OAuth-Verwendung behoben</item>
      <item>Falsch positives Ergebnis beim Server Setup Check behoben</item>
    </admin>
  </whatsNew>
  <whatsNew lang="de_DE">
    <regular>
      <item>Diverse Detailverbesserungen in der Benutzeroberfläche</item>
      <item>Z.B. helle Symbole mit dem dunklen Thema</item>
      <item>oder die Überlappung des Bestätigungs-Button in Kommentaren behoben</item>
    </regular>
    <admin>
      <item>Behandelte Probleme mit ungewöhnlichen Benutzer-IDs</item>
      <item>Fehler beim Web-Logout bei OAuth-Verwendung behoben</item>
      <item>Falsch positives Ergebnis beim Server Setup Check behoben</item>
    </admin>
  </whatsNew>
  <whatsNew lang="es">
    <regular>
      <item>Varias mejores de detalles en la interfaz de usuario</item>
      <item>por ejemplo: iconos con el tema oscuro</item>
      <item>o evitar la superposición del botón de Enviar en comentarios</item>
    </regular>
    <admin>
      <item>Se han tratado problemas con IDs de usuario poco comunes</item>
      <item>Arreglada la desconexión web en el uso de OAuth</item>
      <item>Resuelto un falso positivo en la comprobación de configuración del servidor</item>
    </admin>
  </whatsNew>
  <whatsNew lang="it">
    <regular>
      <item>Diversi miglioramenti di dettagli nell'interfaccia utente</item>
      <item>ad es. icone chiare con tema scuro</item>
      <item>o evita la sovrapposizione del pulsante di invio nei commenti</item>
    </regular>
    <admin>
      <item>Gestiti i problemi con ID utente insoliti</item>
      <item>Corretta disconnessione web utikizzando OAuth</item>
      <item>Risolto falso positivo nel controllo di installazione del server</item>
    </admin>
  </whatsNew>
  <whatsNew lang="nl">
    <regular>
      <item>Diverse detailverbeteringen in de gebruikersinterface</item>
      <item>Bijv. lichte pictogrammen met het donkere thema</item>
      <item>of vermijd overlap in de verwerk-knoppen voor reacties</item>
    </regular>
    <admin>
      <item>Behandelde problemen met ongewone gebruikers ID's</item>
      <item>Vaste web uitloggen bij OAuth gebruik</item>
      <item>Een false positive in de controle van de serverconfiguratie opgelost </item>
    </admin>
  </whatsNew>
  <whatsNew lang="pt_BR">
    <regular>
      <item>Diversas melhorias em detalhes da interface do usuário</item>
      <item>por ex. ícones claros com o tema escuro</item>
      <item>ou evitar a sobreposição do botão de envio nos comentários</item>
    </regular>
    <admin>
      <item>Problemas tratados com IDs de usuário incomuns</item>
      <item>Resolvido o logout da Web por OAuth</item>
      <item>Resolvido falso positivo na verificação de configuração do servidor</item>
    </admin>
  </whatsNew>
  <whatsNew lang="tr">
    <regular>
      <item>Kullanıcı arayüzünde bazı ayrıntılar iyileştirildi</item>
      <item>Örnek: koyu temadaki açık renk simgeler</item>
      <item>ya da yorumlardaki gönder düğmesinin altta kalması</item>
    </regular>
    <admin>
      <item>Kullanıcı kodları ile ilgili rastlanan sorunlar çözüldü</item>
      <item>OAuth kullanılırken web oturumu kapatma sorunu çözüldü</item>
      <item>Sunucu kurulumu denetimleri sırasında yanlış bulunan hata çözümlendi</item>
    </admin>
  </whatsNew>
</release>
